

# **Sohail Aman**

#### Front-End Web-Developer

Hello, I'm a dedicated web developer with over 4 years of experience. I specialize in JavaScript, ReactJS, Firebase, HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap to create responsive and user-friendly websites. I'm committed to staying updated with industry trends and delivering optimized cross-browser-compatible web solutions. Let's bring your web projects to life with innovative technology.

#### **Contact Info**

+92-344-4321-653

sohailaman121@gmail.com

https://vibecoder.netlify.app/

#### **Education**

**Virtual university Pakistan**Current

Senior High School

2020 - 2022

**Junior High School** 

2012 - 2018

**Primary School** 

2004-2012

### **Work Experience**

Senior-Front End Developer2021 - NOW

AT CodeArena Tech Pvt Ltd
Gilgit Baltistan, Pakistan

Junior-Front End Developer 2020 - 2021

AT Zumurs Tech Pvt Ltd
Gilgit Baltistan, Pakistan

#### Skills

#### **Front End Development**

Expert

#### UX/UI Design

Intermediate

#### Front End Development Skills

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- ReactJS
- NextJS
- FireBase
- > SASS/LESS
- > HTML/CSS
- > MaterialUI
- Bootstrap / React-Bootstrap / Reactstrap
- > TailwindCSS
- > API Integrations
- > Git

## UX/UI Design Skills

>> Figma

